repairq.io 2018-02-22

# RepairQ | Privacy Policy

Last updated: July 20, 2017  
ServiceCentral Technologies Inc. d/b/a RepairQ (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the http://repairq.io website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at http://repairq.io

## Information Collection And Use

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, other information (“Personal Information”).

We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services.

## Log Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service’s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

## Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

## Behavioral Remarketing

ServiceCentral Technologies Inc. d/b/a RepairQ uses remarketing services to advertise on third party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

  * GoogleGoogle AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. 

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

  * TwitterTwitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc. 

You can opt-out from Twitter’s interest-based ads by following their instructions: <https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405>

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: <https://twitter.com/privacy>

  * FacebookFacebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc. 

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#568137493302217>

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada <http://youradchoices.ca/> or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>

  * PinterestPinterest remarketing service is provided by Pinterest Inc. 

You can opt-out from Pinterest’s interest-based ads by enabling the “Do Not Track” functionality of your web browser or by following Pinterest instructions: <http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data>

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Pinterest by visiting their Privacy Policy page: <https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy>

  * AdRollAdRoll remarketing service is provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc. 

You can opt-out of AdRoll remarketing by visiting this AdRoll Advertising Preferences web page: [http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false](http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false)

For more information on the privacy practices of AdRoll, please visit the AdRoll Privacy Policy web page: <http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy>

  * Perfect AudiencePerfect Audience remarketing service is provided by NowSpots Inc. 

You can opt-out of Perfect Audience remarketing by visiting these pages: Platform Opt-out (<http://pixel.prfct.co/coo>) and Partner Opt-out (<http://ib.adnxs.com/optout>).

For more information on the privacy practices of Perfect Audience, please visit the Perfect Audience Privacy Policy & Opt-out web page: <https://www.perfectaudience.com/privacy/index.html>

  * AppNexusAppNexus remarketing service is provided by AppNexus Inc. 

You can opt-out of AppNexus remarketing by visiting the Privacy & the AppNexus Platform web page: <http://www.appnexus.com/platform-policy#choices>

For more information on the privacy practices of AppNexus, please visit the AppNexus Platform Privacy Policy web page: <http://www.appnexus.com/platform-policy/>

## Do Not Track Disclosure

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

## Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

## Compliance With Laws

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

## Business Transaction

If ServiceCentral Technologies Inc. d/b/a RepairQ is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred as a business asset. In such cases, we will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and/or becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

## International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children’s Privacy

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 20, 2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
